You know, maybe no one wants to say it, but I'm going to say it.
I think what is also pissing Israelis off who support the Israeli government is that
Palestinians are fine.
Okay.
They fine as hell.
Y'all know that though.
Like, you just can't, you can't argue it.
And it's not, it's like, it's just, they just fine.
They, they, they dancing fly.
They just, they hold energy fly.
Like they fine.
I mean, and it's just like, damn, like as much as we are trying to take you down and
shake you down, like y'all still coming with this, that'd be pissing them the fuck off.
That's why black folks used to show up to the March style down.
Okay.
Giving you a pin curl and a kitten heel, walking, boycotting the bus.
Cause you going to try it, but you ain't going to take our flyness.
You're the bull.
Hello.
You